# **Eric Price**

ericjosprice@gmail.com 512-438-9119

www.linkedin.com/in/ericjprice

www.mvwebsite.com

Born and raised in Austin, Texas. I have a B.A. in Mathematics from The University of Texas at Austin. Driven technologist with nearly a decades worth of managerial experience and a passion for problem solving. I worked for four years at an electronic medical records software company as a Strategic Account Manager. I gained a high level perspective of the operations at hundreds of medical clinics and the software industry. I am currently pursuing a career as a Software Engineer so that I may utilize my skills, experience, and desire to make tools that solve problems for everyone.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## eClinicalWorks - Austin, Texas

Dec 2014 – Feb 2019

Strategic Account Manager / Supervisor 2019

Dec 2017 – Feb

- Led Account Management and Project Management teams to implement large-scale changes across Accountable Care Organizations and Hospitals
- Used JIRA to review status of development tasks and drive progress forward to ensure timely delivery of high priority bug fixes
- Gathered details from healthcare professionals about automating processes via software functional enhancements and relayed specifications to software development teams
- Managed major and minor system changes, upgrades and patches for client hosted servers as well as cloud/SAAS clients
- Recommended strategies to improve clinical efficiency and productivity
- Ensured smooth implementation and product adoption for customers using electronic medical records and practice management solutions
- Participated in departmental training sessions

### Aruss Inc. - Austin, Texas

Jan 2008 – June 2014

May 2010 – June 2014

- Supervisor / Surety Representative
  Managed team of 10 people delegating duties to efficiently conduct operations
- Through research and observation, developed marketing plans using client demographics, which resulted in reduced operating cost
- Increased completion rate of contractual agreements by effectively communicating with clients
- Took initiative to create training procedures boosting the abilities of those representing the company
- Edited and maintained website in order to improve language use and aesthetics

#### **SKILLS**

- Knowledge of Wireshark, TCP/IP, Network Security, DNS, SMTP
- Web development: JavaScript, jQuery, Git, Node.js, React.js, Express.js, MySQL, Laravel
- Leadership: Team-oriented, Creative, Critical thinker, Adaptive, Reliable
- Communication: Customer Service, Sales, Tutoring, Listening

#### **EDUCATION**

### The University of Texas at Austin

Austin, TX

B.A. in Mathematics

Dec 2012

• Certificate Business Foundations Program